i watched
я смотрел
andrey before
андрей до
33 not 40 valente to
33 не 40 валенте по
no 40 were
нет 40 были
before nevian shorter than 15
до nevian короче 15
[music]
[музыка]
maybe shorter your camp like it
можем может быть короче твой стан типа
turns out like i kind of know why they say
получается як я типа знаю почему говорят
and i'm here moo started in this right well
и я здесь моо пущенной в этом праве ну
so you like everyone start on it we  both are
так вы типа всем начинайте по ней мы оба
neutral both are disgusting and you start
нейтрально оба противен и ты начинаешь
exclusive and yet Shivana’s rings are
эксклюзивный и все-таки кольца шиваны
always neutral that he starts the window
всегда нейтрально что он и начинает окно
with operations bombed the Donbass is beautiful like a
с операциями бомбили донбассу красив как
rollback to change this one and then you know I
откате поменять этой а потом знаешь вот
’m choking they come to the Ukrainian
я давлюсь они приходят в украинскую
chat roulette why the dykes there hate and
чат-рулетку зачем дайки там хейтит и
Ukrainians on  parts but heifer briki in
украинцев на части но телкова брики
excess of ichiro dacha are fighting so it
избытке ичиро даче воюют так вот
is and
является и
these girls in them in short it turns out in
эти девки в них короче получается в
one dad in another uncle to reveal in
одной батя в друге дядя выявить в
Ukraine and in the tape, so we started
украине и в ленте по вот мы начали вот
this one on there according to the story there
этого на там по рассказу там
, well, like, I’m also not all invaders
якоже ну типа я тоже не все оккупанты
here  on a warmed up wild one they ride
вот на прогретом дикий этом катаются
like gasoline to fire out just gasolines of
типа бензин выпалить просто бензинов
whom glory is half a thousand like you don’t go anywhere
кого славы полтыщи типа никуда не едешь
to attack like tommy baskets I know we also
в атаку типа tommy корзинки знаю так же
have dad there in short everything is cool
у нас там там папа короче все прикольно
and a knight  it’s just that there the
а рыцарь просто там
other part on you can blow out of there no
другой части на можешь подует из там ни
redness the other half would have thought you were
красноты другая половина бы посчитал вы
n’t there just like that I’m all and then right there,
не там просто так я все а потом же там
well, in short, Sasha in the eyepieces in
праве ну и короче вот саша в окулярах в
the real stubbornly we are for the night and
на реальную упорото мы на ночь и на
yes, so you need to learn a lot  there, a
да так вы надо весьма научиться там на
cadet is revealed in the subject of the school of whiskey
кадета выявляется в тему школа виска
water and
вода и
[music]
[музыка]
hmmm, you could, well, damn the Nazi rzhak,
гммы смогла вы можете ну блин наци ржака
it was real,
было реально
I look
я смотреть
at us, too, in a bowl like a bagato of
на у нас тоже в миску дуже багато
Kharkov ones, and I’m basically on the
харьковских c а я так я в принципе на ю
tube so seriously, then I started tsedek from
тубе так серьезно то начинала цедек из
I decided to do a signet less so serious
печатку менее так серьезного решил
with a dance to the cages to
заняться с танцем клеткам блин
scream and moth there if I know the type of massacre
кричать и моли там если типа резни знаю
with here in the mix they start smaller and shorter
с вот в миксе начинают меньше и короче
there three chicks of the Lena river to the whale beer
там три телки реки лены к киту пиво
out of the plague there with acquaintances I will hurt in
наружу чумных там знакомыми задену в
Ukraine like I know sepo yes and rzh youtube
украине типа знаю sepo да и ржу youtube
and that's it  kids also in rubles and he
и все детки тоже рублях а он это
will show their belly in a funny way close the taboo they
прикольно покажет их живот зарасай табу
will send like a military ukraine a chestnut
пошлют типа войсковых украины каштан
I will write to send I want all the coffee
напишу на пошлю я хочу весь кофе
your new one has ended on google and in cs instead of
твоя новая на google и в cs вместо
aleysk she was there she stayed there what for a
алейск был она там пробыла какой стати
poet  like aleysk there is 28000 nasal
поэту по типу алейск там 28000 носовая
here up to 28000 nasal so of course there the
вот до 28000 носовая так разумеется там
Soviet part needs five thousand cal
советского части надо тысяч пять ческих
there, in fact temples and parts on the grid you
там то по сути висков и части на сетке
know instead I create a chip from succession
знаешь вместо я творю чип от преемство
so there is shorter all of these there with a turn
так там короче все этих там оборотом
to listen to both non-relatives to
слушать обоих не родичи короче там
serve there and  so on, then he and everything
служить и так далее то и он и все вот
that is forgotten with us and give this forgotten
этим забытым у нас и дать этому забытому
damn Altai Territory so and here
блин алтайском крае так и вот тут
Ukraine black 5000 kilometers prominent so
украина black 5000 километров видных так
there are 654 homelands and you want to give them and and like
там 654 родины и хотите дать им и и типа
here it is America a badge-fly I don’t
вот она-то америка бляха-муха я не
know  plus
знаете плюс
lessons before the bombas demobilization and like where you
уроки до дембеля bombas и типа где вы
were eight years old you can type from and from type
были восемь лет можно типа от и от типа
don’t sour Abbasov with anyone you tube write
с кем не кисни аббасов ю тубе напишешь
me there with a disk of cogs the court admitted
мне там диском винтики суде признал
we want good
хотим добра
you can sell the fifth vidos comment above
можно продать пятым видосом коммент выше
to
to
provide I’ll write from Kharkov I understand
provide я с харькова напишешь я понимаю
that  you oh
что ты о
and everything sous here is
и все су тут
shorter and then the secret is to [ __ ], I think
короче и тогда секрет выебать я думаю
damn you with whom from the fetters meant the threads there
блин ты с кем из пут означало нитки там
directly with a view just c vedalife to we will
прям видом просто c vedalife к мы
learn how to accelerate with and remind
поучимся разгоняться с и напоминать
in general recommendations
вообще рекомендации
recommendation
рекомендация
cool  oh
прикольно
yes was given with this tetra is the same yes
да далась с этом тетра это же да
.
.
[music]
[музыка]
ok
ok
good good let the soul straight smoke not
добрый хорошо давай душу прямо дым не
so pleased in the cross to realize I'm like a
так порадовал в кроссе осознать я так
tank like vidos where there rivers of tar is
бачек типа видосы куда там реки смолина
useful guitarist like you know the batch,
пригодится гитариста типа знаешь батчате
so like
поэтому типа
and type the guitarist is the guitarist of
и типом малый там гитарист гитарист
this batch, well,
этого батчата ну а
I'm shorter, I kind of think it means and still
я короче я типа думаю значит и таки
right away you’re butterflies damn it there this is a
сразу этом ты бабочек блин там вот это
trap for yourself it’s kind of say the stage of the
капкан за себя это вида сказать этапе
day we have three everything glory to ukraine
дня у нас три все слава украине на эту
gave me this one and
меня дала и
this happens
такое бывает